Mi lómë cemessë,
In the silence of the earth,
yassë súrë yesta,
where the wind begins to call,
síressë, ëarissë,
by the river, by the sea,
nórë nu lómë esta
there’s a hidden world for all
Mi taurë lómëa nu,
Through the forest, dark and deep,
oronti or i alta,
past the mountains standing high,
síressë yassë lumbor caita,
by the lake where shadows sleep,
menel nu pella
underneath the open sky
Aiwi lírir mi súrë,
Trees are whispering in the air,
lótë liltë calaressë,
Flowers dancing in the light,
sarnë caita nárë,
Rocks are resting everywhere,
tulir lindalë lómessë
Guiding travelers through the night
Nén sirya ar uru calë,
Water flows and fire burns,
cemë tulca nu talma,
Earth is strong beneath our feet,
súrë orta ar váta,
Wind will rise and slowly turn,
vilya ar menel ar ilya
Air and sky and all we meet
Olvar orta ar rávar norta,
Plants will grow and animals run,
fanyar hosta mi luinë,
Clouds will gather in the blue,
lossë lanta ar anar túra,
Rain will fall, then comes the sun,
caitalë ilyë lírë
Painting life in every hue
Raumo tula, hlarë rómë,
Storm is coming, hear the sound,
calma rista menel,
Lightning cuts across the sky,
lossë ar aiwë lanta cemen,
Snow and hail fall to the ground,
valiëa túrë orta
Nature’s power rising high
Ar lómë enta tula,
Then the silence comes again,
isil or ar eleni cala,
Moon above and stars so bright,
mi i nórë varya ar auta,
In this world of loss and gain,
nárë lindë aurë ar lómë
Nature sings… through day and night
Mi lómë cemessë,
In the silence of the earth,
yassë súrë yesta,
where the wind begins to call,
síressë, ëarissë,
by the river, by the sea,
nórë nu lómë esta
there’s a hidden world for all
Mi taurë lómëa nu,
Through the forest, dark and deep,
oronti or i alta,
past the mountains standing high,
síressë yassë lumbor caita,
by the lake where shadows sleep,
menel nu pella
underneath the open sky
Aiwi lírir mi súrë,
Trees are whispering in the air,
lótë liltë calaressë,
Flowers dancing in the light,
sarnë caita nárë,
Rocks are resting everywhere,
tulir lindalë lómessë
Guiding travelers through the night
Nén sirya ar uru calë,
Water flows and fire burns,
cemë tulca nu talma,
Earth is strong beneath our feet,
súrë orta ar váta,
Wind will rise and slowly turn,
vilya ar menel ar ilya
Air and sky and all we meet
Olvar orta ar rávar norta,
Plants will grow and animals run,
fanyar hosta mi luinë,
Clouds will gather in the blue,
lossë lanta ar anar túra,
Rain will fall, then comes the sun,
caitalë ilyë lírë
Painting life in every hue
Raumo tula, hlarë rómë,
Storm is coming, hear the sound,
calma rista menel,
Lightning cuts across the sky,
lossë ar aiwë lanta cemen,
Snow and hail fall to the ground,
valiëa túrë orta
Nature’s power rising high
Ar lómë enta tula,
Then the silence comes again,
isil or ar eleni cala,
Moon above and stars so bright,
mi i nórë varya ar auta,
In this world of loss and gain,
nárë lindë aurë ar lómë
Nature sings… through day and night