Clap your hands — move your feet,
Jump up high — feel the beat,
Turn around — don’t be slow,
Come on now — here we go!
Walk, run — stop, then go,
Stand up straight, then bend down low,
Look around, touch the ground,
Make a sound — louder now!
Say “go!” — (GO!)
Say “stop!” — (STOP!)
Move fast — don’t drop!
Clap your hands — move your feet,
Jump up high — feel the beat,
Turn around — don’t be slow,
Come on now — here we go!
Open, close — push, pull,
Take it easy, now go full,
Sit down, stand — left, right,
Keep it moving — feel the light!
Faster now — don’t wait,
Move your body — feel great,
Up and down — side to side,
Let the rhythm be your guide
Clap your hands — move your feet,
Jump up high — feel the beat,
Turn around — shout it loud,
You’re alive — feel it now!